The kinds of weather that I like best, I think the best time a year is the fall,
我最喜欢的天气, 我想一年中最好的时候是秋天,
that time a year where the air is crisp and cool and it seems to be cleaner.
一年中的这个季节空气清新, 凉爽, 感觉更干净.
Spring is my favourite kind of weather.
春天是我最喜欢的季节.
I like this weather. Today is a perfect day.
我喜欢现在这样的天气, 今天好极了.
Not too hot, not too cool, you can do things outside.
不是太热, 也不是太冷, 可以在户外活动.
We live, unfortunately, in Washington D. C. which has sort of two weathers: bad and hot.
不幸的是, 我们住在Washington D.C, 那里有两种天气: 坏天气和热天气.
Winter, a little bit of winter but not really, and then mostly very, very hot summer.
冬天并不像真正的冬天, 而夏天却非常非常炎热.
I love the autumn here, and actually the past couple of years we've been having really nice falls.
我喜欢这儿的秋天, 过去几年的秋天真是不错.
I usually watch the weather channel.
我通常会看天气频道.
The paper. On the news. Yes, news, weather channel.
报纸上有, 新闻中也有. 对, 新闻和天气频道.
I like to watch them when they give you the weather report showing the map of the whole country
我喜欢看天气预报, 他们在播天气预报时还同时展示全国地图.
and you can then see the weather systems, weather moving.
你能看到天气系统和天气在变化.
I look at the newspaper and then l look outside and see, er, which, which is a better predictor.
我看看报纸, 然后看看外面的天, 比较一下谁预报更准.
There's a free weather, er, phone number that you can call for like a recorded weather forecast and I call probably two or three times a day.
有个查询天气的免费电话, 拨通电话后有天气预报的录音, 我每天都要打两三次.
I do. I have to know what to wear, you know.
是真的. 我得知道穿什么衣服, you know.
It changes so quickly that it doesn't really matter what the weather forecasts say.
天气说变就变, 天气预报怎么说并不起多大作用.
If I wake up in the morning needing to go to work and it's raining, that, kind of dampens my spirits a little bit.
如果我一早起来要去工作, 天在下雨, 那, 这种天气会使我情绪有点儿低落.
I think if it's a nice, crisp, cool morning, the sun is shining, you feel, you feel bright and cheery yourself.
我想如果早晨空气清新凉爽, 阳光明媚, 你就会感到轻松愉快, 兴高采烈.
The sun is very energizing.
阳光使人精力充沛.
I couldn't live somewhere where it's rainy or cold all the time.
我不能住在总是下雨或阴冷的地方.
When it's hot and humid in Washington, we don't want to do anything and,
在Washington又热又湿时, 我们什么都不想做,
you know, I think yesterday was a really rainy, you know, overcast day, everybody was a little down.
you know, 昨天下雨, you know, 天阴沉沉的, 每个人心情都不好.
Today it's beautiful, so we're all up again.
今天天好了, 我们又都振作了起来.